Greenbaum, Marcia Arbitration Files 6208
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Marcia Greenbaum Arbitration Files
1977-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Greenbaum, Marcia
6208
44.5 cubic feet
22 linear ft.
Records.
8258619
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 12, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration and award; Greenbaum, Marcia
8258619
- Nova Law Review; Drugs and Alcohol Testing. (Box 1)
  - Mass. BD. Of Community Colleges and Direct-ARB 1977 Mass. Teachers Assn. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mass. BD of Regnl Community Colleges and Direct ARB 1977 QUINSIGAMONDMCCC (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Nova Law Review Vol. 11 No. 2 Winter 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts; Massachusetts Organization of State Engineers and Scientists, 1978. (Box 2)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts Board of Conciliation and Arbitration PS-66-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts and MBC&A PS-66-1978 Fact Finding (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth of Mass. Board of Coalition & Arbitration PF-63-1977 Fact Finder's Report & Recommendation; Decision (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth of Mas. And M.O.S.E.S. Brief on Behalf of M.O.S.E.S. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alliance Contract July 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - An Analysis & Comparison of Engineering ad Scientific Salaries Paid by the Commonwealth of Mass. (M.O.S.E.S. exhibit 31) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - M.O.S.E.S. Proposals (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - M.O.S.E.S. Exhibit 3 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - MOSES Exhibit 4 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - MOSES Exhibits 5-30, 33B, 42 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - MOSES Employer's Brief 8/14/1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Commonwealth Exhibits 1-45 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 2 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 3 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 6 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 7 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 4 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 5 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 8 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 9 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 9 (Evening Session) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 10 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 11 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 12 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Commonwealth of Mass v. MOSES Stenographic Record Vol. 13 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Williams v. University of Iowa - Employment Arbitration; Arbitration 1993, 1994-1997. (Box 3)
  - Memorial Hospital and AAA #10 300 0168 93 vacancy FMHP, Local 5082 (1993) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - University of Mass and UAW, Local 2322 Health Plan (1993) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Melville Corp. Truck Drivers Local 170 (1993) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - University of Iowa Department of Anatomy Review (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - University of Iowa Department of Anatomy Arbitration Exhibits (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - University of Iowa Arbitration Exhibits (1 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - University of Iowa Arbitration Exhibits (2 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - University of Iowa Arbitration Exhibits (3 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - University of Iowa Arbitration Transcript (pg. 372-534) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - University of Iowa Arbitration Transcript (p. 178-371) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - University of Iowa Arbitration Transcript (pg. 1-177) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Williams 8-16-94 Condenselt (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Williams 8-17-94 Condenselt (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Williams 8-18-94 Condenselt (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Williams v. University of Iowa 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Massachusetts Higher Education Arbitration; Coordinating Council and Fitchburg State College; Massachusetts State College Association; Tod Slone Evaluation and Reappointment, 1995. (Box 4)
  - Mass. Higher Education Coordinating Council and Fitchburg State College (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mass. State College Assoc. v. Higher Education Council Vol. 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mass. State College Assoc. v. Higher Education Coordinating Council Vol. 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Mass. State College Assoc. v. Higher Education Coordinating Council Vol. 3 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Mass. State College Assoc. v. Higher Education Coordinating Council Vol. 4 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Mass. State College Assoc. v. Higher Education Coordinating Council Vol. 5 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Fitchburg State College Information (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Fitchburg State College Information Part 2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Mass. State College Assoc. v. Higher Education Coordinating Council - Assn. Exhibits (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fitchburg State College - Slone Exhibits 1 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fitchburg State College - Slone 2 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Fitchburg State College 3 of 3 (Ad Hoc Evaluation) (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Cloutier and Genrad Employee Arbitration - transcripts, 1998. (Box 5)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. American Arbitration Association (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 1 (Condensed) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Vol. 2 (Condensed) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 3 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 3 (Condensed) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 4 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 4 (Condensed) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 5 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 5 (Condensed) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 6 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 6 (Condensed) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 7 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 7 (Condensed) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 8 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 8 (Condensed) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 9 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 9 (Condensed) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 10 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 10 (Condensed) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 11 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Record Vol. 11 (Condensed) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - AAA Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Background (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Cloutier and Genrad Employee Arbitration - file and exhibits, 1998. (Box 6)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. AAA Payment (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Notes (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad AAA Empl. ARB (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Opinion and Reward (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Memorandum of Law and Complainant's Request for Finding of Fact and Conclusion of Law (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Finding of Facts and Post-Hearing Brief (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Exhibits and References (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Related Cases and Statutes (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Complaintant's Exhibits (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Complaintant's Exhibits Part 2 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Respondent's Exhibits (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Floppy Disks (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Opinion (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Arbitration Opinion and Award (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Opinion and Award Part 2 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad Opinion and Award 3 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cloutier v. Genrad, Inc. Opinion and Award 4 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Arbitration A - M, 2000. (Box 7)
  - Town of Andover DPW and AAA Carver AFSCME Council 93 Local 1704 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Town of Andover, MA and AAA Louis AFSCME Council 93 Pollenites (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Bell Atlantic and AAA Lenigan IBEW Local 2320 Susp. And Terminatr (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - BICC General and FMCS Job Changes Unite Local 1156T (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - E. Stephen Briggs Recommendation and Internal Disciple of GC Connecticut (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Town of Brookline, MA. And Ind. Union of Police Assn. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Brown University and AAA SEIU Local 134 double time pay (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Brown University and AAA SEIU Local 134 written warnings (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Center for Optimum Care and AAA Barnett New England Health Care EES (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Central Falls, RI and AAA IAFF, Local 1485 Pension Contribution (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Central Maine Power Company and AAA IBEW, Local 1837 Transmission Work (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chelsea Place and AAA NERCEU Imogene Fuller (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Coca Cola and AAA Local 1035 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Coca Cola Bottling Co. and AAA Christine DiMartino (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Connecticut Natural Gas and AAA CIUW (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Expedited Inst. AFSCME Council 4 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR File AFSCME (NP-4 Unit) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - State of Connecticut and OLF AFSCME Council 4 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Cleopatra Myers (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR David Melchionne (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR R. Hanson (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Paul Bernard (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR G. Guerrero (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR P-2 S&HS (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Linda Carson (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Barbara Pawlow (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Paul Bernard (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR A. Johnson (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Rick Gomez (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR AFSCME Council 4 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Eliz. Anderson (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR F. Sadlosky (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Danbury Hospital and AAA Danbury Hospital Professional Nurses (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Florida Power Corporation IBEW System Council (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Formtek and FMCS Local 2336 Timeliness and Evaluations (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Frito-Lay Inc. and Orlando, FL Kim Bright (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Greenery at Cheschire and AAA Latasha James (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Hartford Board of Education and AAA HFT & Secs. Beaudoin-Giocoeches (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Hartford, CT Board of Ed. Hartford Fed. Of Teachers (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Hayes v. Suffolk County Sheriff Dept. (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Hormel Foods Corp. Local 1996 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Jewish Home for the Aged and the AAA (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Kanzaki Specialty Papers and AAA (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - University of Mass. And AAA Local 2322 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Merck-Medco RX Services Local 3-984 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - WFSB-TV and AAA Vacation Weeks (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Mississippi Power Local 1209 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Arbitration M - W, 2000. (Box 8)
  - Monroe, CT Board of Education and AAA Local 1303-167 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Morganite Crucible and USWA Local 134 Villanueva Discharge (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Morton International Inc. and Local 1760 Terry Hayes (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - New Britain Consolidated School and AAA (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Town of North Providence and AAA Local 2334 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Norwich, CT Board of Ed. And AAA Municipal EES Union Intl. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Perrier Group of America and Poland Spring Local 1445 Grenier Discharge (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Portsmouth, RI School Comm. And AAA Sick Leave (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Quinnipiac University and AAA (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - State of Rhode Island and AAA Local 580 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - State of Rhode Island and AAA Dept. of Health (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Rhode Island Hospital and AAA Local 5098 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Rhode Island Hospital and AAA Albert Jacavone (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Rhode Island Hospital and AAA DeGaetano Term. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Rhode Island Hospital and AAA Teamsters Local 251 S. Barone (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Rhode Island Hospital and AAA Teamsters Local 251 A. Castro (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - University of Rhode Island and AAUP (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Rogers Corporation and AAA Local 1-1554 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Salem, MA School Committee and AAA Salem Teachers Assoc. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Salem School Committee and AAA Salem Teachers Union Local 1258 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Schweitzer-Maudit and FMCS Hudson Falls, NY (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. Local 791 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Sodexho/Marriott School Food Serv. And AAA Local 226 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Southworth-Milton Inc. and AAA Local 447 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - City of Springfield, Mass. And AAA Springfield Assn. of Municipal ES (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Sprint and Local 199 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Sprint and Local 1649 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Tamko Roofing Products Local 8681 J. Phipps Dischr. (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Union Leader Corp. and AAA Manchester Newspaper Guild 167 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - United Parcel Service and FMCS Local 402 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - US Airways System and SBA (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - US Dept. of the Navy Naval Undersea Warfare Center Local R1-144 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - US Tusbaki Inc. Local 7912 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - US Tsubaki Inc. Local 7912 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Warwick, RI and AAA Local 2748 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Wheland Foundry Local 3967 Overtime Pay (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Windham Hospital and AAA Windham United Employees L. 5099 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Windham Hospital and AAA Windham United EES Local 5099 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Arbitration, 2001. (Box 9)
  - City of Sanford, FL and FMCS Fraternal Order of Police Force (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - FDLE Criminal Report - Seifert 1 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - FDLE Criminal Report - Siefert 2 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - FDLE Criminal Report - Seifert 3 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - FDLE Criminal Report - Seifert 4 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Admin. Investigations 1 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Admin. Investigations 2 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Admin. Investigations 3 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Admin. Investigations 4 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - SAPPI and AAA Local Lodge 2740 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - SAPPI and AAA local 1-1069 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Ameritech and SIPP local union 21 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Smith House and AAA Gwen Armstrong (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Stop and Shop Supermarkets and AAA Local 919 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - US Airways and SBA P. Gorman (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - TRUE Temper Sports and United Steel Workers District 9 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - US Airways and SBA K. Vikroy (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Verizon and MREP Kerry Vachon (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Verizon and MREP Lisa Albanese (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Tandet Center for Continuing Care and AAA J. Daniels Termin. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - US Airways and SBA C. Lindsay (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Waterbury Hospital and AAA Paquin Promotion (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Arbitration A - L, 2001. (Box 10)
  - Alternative Services and AAA Williams Termination (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Central Maine Power Company v. Local 1837 1 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Central Maine Power v. Local 1837 E. Dulac (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Central Maine Power Company v. Local 1837 2 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Central Maine Power Company v. Local 1837 3 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Circuitwise Inc. and AAA United Elec., Radio and MWA 299 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Coca Cola and AAA Local 1035 Transfer and Sen. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - State of Connecticut and AFSCME Council 4 Richard Gajda (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 Richard Hurley (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 Michele Dickens (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 Glenn Hank (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 Institutional (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 Haley Ruscoe (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 G. Guererro 30 Day Suspension (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 Michelle Lowman (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 N. Rodriguez (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 Dan Wynne (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 Arlene Jilot (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 Sara Ortiz (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 Institutional (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 Denis Coley (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - State of Connecticut and OLR Council 4 Institutional Local 2663 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - State of Connecticut and Educational Admrs. Connecticut Sate Employees Assn. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Uconn Health Center and AAA University Health Profiles NJG (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Danbury Hospital and AAA DHProf. Nurses Assn. (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Florida Power Corporation and FMCS Hernandez (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - GAF Building Materials Corp. and AAA Local 25 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Hannaford Bros. Co. and AAA Local 1445 Ken Leighton (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Harvard Vanguard Medical Ass. And AAA Local 285 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - HMS Host and FMCS Here. Local 355 Ana Marques (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Jackson Memorial Hospital and FMCS Local 1991 Pharmacist (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Landmark Medical Center and AAA (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Landmark Medical Center and AAA Local 5067 Pharmacy and Nuclear Med. (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Lockheed Martin Aeronautics and FMCS Local 615 R.L. Bissell (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Arbitration M - R, 2001. (Box 11)
  - Madico Inc. and AAA Local 262 Stephen Desharnais (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mariner Healthcare and AAA District 1199 Termination (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Electric Co. Local 446 Ron Porecca Grievance (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Electric Co. Local 486 TDI Tax (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Trial Court and AAA Local 254 Curtis Termination (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Meggit Avionics and AAA Barbara Robitaill (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Miami Dade Community College and FMCS SEIU Local (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Mississippi Power Co. and FMCS Local 1211 Discharge (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Mississippi Power Company Grievance Hearing of Gregory Croon Wrongful Termination Proceedings (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Narragansett, RI School Committee and AAA (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - National Grid USA Service Co. and Temporary Working Foreman Local 486 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - New England Confectionary Co. and AAA Local 348 Termination (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Town of North Providence, RI and AAA Local 2334 Vacancies (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Northshore Ambulance and AAA Local 42 Alan McAlpine Lost Work (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Northshore Ambulance and AAA Local 42 Kevin Sheridan Uniform (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - City of Pawtucket, RI and AAA Firefighters (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Praxair, Inc. and FMCS Local 3 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Quinnipiac University Faculty Fedn. Day (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Rockbestos and AAA Local 1370 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Rogers Corporation and AAA Local 1-46 Carl Cayan (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Interest Arbitration - Connecticut/CSEA Criminal Justice, 2001. (Box 12)
  - Donn. Division of Criminal Justice and Interest Arbitration Police Inspectors (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Conn. Division of Justice and Interest Arbitration CSEA Police Inspectors Part 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Conn. Division of Criminal Justice and Interest Arbitration Award (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Conn. Division of Criminal Justice Police Inspectors Council Interest Arbitration, Materials of the Division (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Conn. Division of Criminal Justice and Interest Arbitration Resolved Issues (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Arbitration - United States Department of Justice Federal Bureau of Prisons, 2001. (Box 13)
  - US Dept. of Justice Federal Bureau of Prisons and Local 4052 Decision (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - US Federal Bureau of Prisons and FMCS Local 4052 Harassment, Unprofessional conduct (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - US Dept. of Justice Federal Bureau of Prisons Sexual Harassment Arbitration Opinion and Award (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - US Army Engineers and Local 1124 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - US Department of Justice Federal Bureau of Prisons and Local 4052 Reply to Arbitrator's Remanded Issues (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Dept. of Justice Federal Bureau of Prisons v. Local 4052 Information (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Dept. of Justice Federal Bureau of Prisons v. Local 4052 Union Attachments (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Calculating Damages and Other Remedies in Employment Disputes (Burns and McCausland) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Dept. of Justice Federal Bureau of Prisons Extra Info (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Local 4052 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Local 4052 Union Exhibits (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Detention Center Rosters (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Verizon Bell Atlantic Local 1400 Gerald Gentile (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Interest Arbitration - Conn/CSEA - P3A, 2001. (Box 14)
  - State of Connecticut and Connecticut State Employees Association (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - State of Connecticut and Connecticut State Employee Association (CSEA) Brief for the State of Connecticut (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - State of Connecticut and CSEA Joint Exhibits 4, 27-29 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - State of Connecticut and CSEA Resolved Issues (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - State of Connecticut and CSEA Initial Proposals and Contracts (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - State of Connecticut and CSEA Joint Exhibits 17 and 19 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - NP-2 94-97, State of Connecticut and CSEA Joint Exhibit 21 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - State of Connecticut and CSEA Joint Exhibits 23 and 26 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - State of Connecticut and CSEA Joint Exhibit 24 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - State of Connecticut and CSEA Joint Exhibit 30 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Joint Exhibits 31-50 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - State of Connecticut and Local 511 Opinion and Award (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - State of Connecticut CSEA Exhibits P-3A (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - State of Connecticut and CSEA State Exhibits P-3A (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - P-3A 2001 Arbitration (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - State Exhibit #1 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Arbitration A - C, 2002. (Box 15)
  - Amherst, MA School Dept. and AAA Amherst Education Assn. Deschenes Evaluation (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Aramark Services, Inc. and FMCS Local 769 Fleet Policy (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Say State Gas Company and AAA USWA Unjust Termination Chadden (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Bay State Gas Company and AAA USWA Local 12026 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Blackstone-Millville And AAA Peter Fedyszyn (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Boston Public Health Commission and AAA Local 9158 Sick Leave Policy (Box 15, Folder 6)